Guide to the Raymond Philip Morris Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Biographical Material, Series IV
  - Letterbook: A tribute to Raymond P. Morris, presented to Raymond P. Morris by the Alumni Council of the Yale Divinity School, April 19, 1972. (Box OV2)